fundtrackersql.com 2018-01-08

# FundTracker Sql Web System

Privacy Policy

Pics takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

NOTICE: [Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.

  * This policy covers how Pics treats personal information that Pics collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Pics products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Pics does not own or control, or to people that Pics does not employ or manage. 

  * Pics collects personal information when you register with Pics, when you use Pics products or services, when you visit Pics pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Pics may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some products and services we might also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. When you register with Pics and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Pics collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 
  * Pics automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Pics cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * Pics uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

  * Pics does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Pics under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Pics communicate with you about offers from Pics and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Pics terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if Pics is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Yahoo! will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

  * Pics may set and access Pics cookies on your computer. 

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

  * Pics may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Pics account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please visit our contact page.
